Alumni Association; Records ua801
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1851-2005; Undated; 3; 10.21 cubic ft.
  - History of the State Teachers College Alumni Association by Margaret Brown, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Late 19th Century Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Mauritz Johnson at Curriculum Conference Photograph, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Memento Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Metro New York Chapter, Happy Hour "Name that Joint" Photographs and Negatives, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Metro New York Chapter Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Miss Gertrude Schermerhorn, Undated; VHS Tape (Video-tape 1)
  - National Capital Chapter Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Oldies, Undated (Reel 4)
  - Oneonta Chapter Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Photograph of Jackson, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Photograph of Johnson, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Unidentified Alumni and Student Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Unidentified Mounted Yearbook Pages, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Watercolor Prints Mailer, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - West Central Florida Chapter Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
- Class Notes and Communication, 1859-2011; Undated; 4; 4.52 cubic ft.
  This series contains correspondence as well as pamphlets and other materials distributed to alumni, predominantly for reunions and other key events. The earliest materials are from 19th Century jubilees and reunions of all classes on Alumni Day. Later alumni held reunions only for specific classes or campus organizations, such as the Potter Club or Pep Band, and this is reflected in the more targeted correspondence. Please see Series 1 and Series 3 for more materials related to Alumni Day, and Series 1 for communication to members of the Eastern Branch of the Alumni Association. The correspondence was retained with the group's meeting minutes and is therefore located in Administration.
  There also are two publications, The Echo and the Alumni Quarterly, with contributions by, relevant to or about alumni. Introduced in 1892 as a monthly publication, The Echo was a newspaper/literary magazine featuring short stories and poems by current students or alumni as well news updates about the college, faculty, current students and alumni. Beginning in 1919, the Alumni Quarterly appeared four times a year, once each season. Although it still featured written contributions and news about faculty and current students, the emphasis shifted to news about and for alumni. The publication sought to bring together graduates of "old Normal" (State Normal School), the Normal College and the State College for Teachers. The issues included articles about events like Homecoming, contact information for key alumni contacts such as the leadership of the Alumni Association and branch associaitons and news about alumni jobs, births, marriages and deaths. Although alumni always served on the editorial board, by 1933 the publication specifically states that it is published by the Alumni Association. The Echo continued as a literary magazine and some later issues are included in this series. The Alumni Association replaced the Alumni Quarterly with The Carillon, another quarterly alumni publication in Fall 1967 as a tribute to the Carillon tower built with alumni funds on the University's new Uptown Campus.
  - Association of Graduates, Sixth Biennial Meeting, 1859 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Reunion, 1867 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Reunion, 1883 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 3)
  - Alumni Reunion, 1885 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 4)
  - Search for Missing Alumni Mailing Addresses, ca. 1889 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 5)
  - The Normal College Echo, Vol. 1, No. 7, 1893 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 6)
  - The Normal College Echo, Vol. 2, No. 4 (4 copies), 1893 November (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 7)
  - The Normal College Echo, Vol. 2, No. 5, 1893 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 8)
  - Semi-Centennial Anniversary, 1893-1894 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 9)
  - The Normal College Echo, Vol. 2, No. 7, 1894 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 10)
  - Semi-Centennial Jubilee and Alumni Association Short History, 1894 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 11)
  - Alumni Reunion, 1900 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 12)
  - The Echo, Vol. 11, No. 5 (4 copies), 1903 January (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 13)
  - The Echo, Vol. 14, No. 5, 1906 January (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 14)
  - The Echo, Vol. 16, No. 9, 1908 May (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 15)
  - The Echo, Vol. 17, No. 1, 1908 October (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 16)
  - Class of 1858, 1908 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 17)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVII, No. 7, 1909 April (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 18)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVII, No. 8, 1909 May (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 19)
  - The Echo, Vol. 17, No. 9, 1909 June (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 20)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVIII, No. 1, 1909 October (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 21)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVIII, No. 4-5, 1910 January-1910 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 22)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVIII, No. 6, 1910 March (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 23)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVIII, No. 7, 1910 April (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 24)
  - The Echo, Vol. XVIII, No. 8, 1910 May (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 25)
  - The Echo, Vol. XIX, No. 2, 1910 October (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 26)
  - The Echo, Vol. XIX, No. 3, 1910 November (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 27)
  - The Echo, Vol. XIX, No. 4, 1910 December (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 28)
  - The Echo, Pg. 241-242, 1911 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 29)
  - The Echo, Vol. 20, No. 8, 1911 June (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 30)
  - The Echo, Pg. 69-72, 1911 October (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 31)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 3 (Also includes Dollhouse program), 1911 November (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 32)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 4, 1911 December (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 33)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 5, 1912 January (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 34)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 6, 1912 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 35)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 7, 1912 March (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 36)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 8, 1912 April (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 37)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 9, 1912 May (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 38)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 10, 1912 June (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 39)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 2, 1912 October (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 40)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 3, 1912 November (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 41)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXII, No. 9, 1913 May (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 42)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIII, No. 1, 1913 September (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 43)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIII, No. 3, 1913 November (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 44)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIII, No. 4, 1913 December (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 45)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIII, No. 5, 1914 January (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 46)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXV, No. 6, 1916 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 47)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXV, No. 7, 1916 March (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 48)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIX, No. 2, 1917 November (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 49)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIX, No. 3, 1917 December (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 50)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIX, No. 4, 1918 January (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 51)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIX, No. 6, 1918 February (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 52)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIX, No. 7, 1918 March (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 53)
  - The Echo, Vol. XXIX, No. 8, 1918 April (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 54)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1919 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 55)
  - Letters from Alumni Association President Mary E. Cameron, 1919-1920 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 56)
  - Alumni Quarterly Brochure, ca. 1919 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 57)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1920 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 58)
  - World War I Memorial Correspondence, 1920 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 59)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1921 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 60)
  - Proofs of Alumni Quarterly, 1921 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 61)
  - New York City Branch, 1921; 1980 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 62)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1922 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 63)
  - Alumni Reunions, 1922-1924 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 64)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1923 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 65)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1924 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 66)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1925 (Box 1 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 67)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1926 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1927 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1928 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 3)
  - The Echo, 1928-1929 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 4)
  - The Echo, Vol. XI, No.2, 1929 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 5)
  - The Echo, Vol. XI, No.3, 1929 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 6)
  - The Echo, Vol. XI, No.4, 1929 June (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 7)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1929 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 8)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1930 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 9)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1931 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 10)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1932 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 11)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1933 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 12)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1934 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 13)
  - Special Committee on Membership Mailer, 1934 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 14)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1935 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 15)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1936 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 16)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1937 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 17)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1938 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 18)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1939 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 19)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1940 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 20)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1941 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 21)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1942 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 22)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1943 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 23)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1944 February (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 24)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1944 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 25)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1944 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 26)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1945 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 27)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1945 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 28)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1945 Summer (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 29)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1945 Fall (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 30)
  - Letter Regarding Cancellation of Alumni Day Due to World War, ca. 1945 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 31)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1946 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 32)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1946 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 33)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1946 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 34)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1946 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 35)
  - Alumni Membership Blank Application, ca. 1946 (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 36)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1947 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 37)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1947 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 38)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1947 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 39)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1947 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 40)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1948 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 41)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1948 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 42)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1948 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 43)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1948 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 44)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1949 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 45)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1949 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 46)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1949 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 47)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1949 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 48)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1950 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 49)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1950 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 50)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1950 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 51)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1950 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 52)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1951 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 53)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1951 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 54)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1951 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 55)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1951 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 56)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1952 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 57)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1952 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 58)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1952 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 59)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1952 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 60)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1953 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 61)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1953 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 62)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1953 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 63)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1953 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 64)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1954 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 65)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1954 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 66)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1954 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 67)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1954 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 68)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1955 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 69)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1955 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 70)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1955 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 71)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1955 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 72)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1956 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 73)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1956 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 74)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1956 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 75)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1956 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 76)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1957 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 77)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1957 April (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 78)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1957 July (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 79)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1957 October (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 80)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1958 January (Box 2 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 81)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1958 April (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1958 July (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1958 October (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 3)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1959 January (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 4)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1959 April (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 5)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1959 July (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 6)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1959 October (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 7)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1960 January (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 8)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1960 April (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 9)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1960 July (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 10)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1960 October (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 11)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1961 January (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 12)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1961 April (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 13)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1961 July (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 14)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1961 October (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 15)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1962 January (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 16)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1962 April (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 17)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1962 July (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 18)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1962 October (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 19)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1963 January (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 20)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1963 April (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 21)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1963 Summer (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 22)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1963 Fall (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 23)
  - Long Island Branch, 1963 Fall; 1973-1975; 1977-1980; 1983-1985 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 24)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1964 Winter (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 25)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1964 Spring (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 26)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1964 Summer (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 27)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1964 Fall (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 28)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1965 Winter (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 29)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1965 Spring (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 30)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1965 Summer (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 31)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1965 Fall (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 32)
  - Class of 1945 Newsletters and Reunions, 1965-2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence, 1965; 1970-1973 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 34)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1966 Winter (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 35)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1966 Spring (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 36)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1966 Summer (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 37)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1966 Fall (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 38)
  - Class of 1936 Newsletters and Reunions, 1966-1985 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 39)
  - Alumni Quarterly, 1967 Spring (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 40)
  - The Carillon, 1968-1986 (Oversized 8)
  - Class of 1927 Newsletters and Reunions, 1968-1996 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 41)
  - Class of 1944 Newsletters and Reunions, 1969-2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 42)
  - Class of 1947 Newsletters and Reunions, 1969-2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 43)
  - Class of 1949 Newsletters and Reunions, 1969-2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 44)
  - Class of 1960 Newsletters and Reunions, ca. 1969-1994 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 45)
  - Class of 1968 Newsletters and Reunions, 1970-1976; 1983; 1993; 2003 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 46)
  - Class of 1940 Newsletters and Reunions, 1970-2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 47)
  - Class of 1965 Newsletters, 1971-1972; 1974-1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 48)
  - Class of 1951 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1972; 1974; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 49)
  - Class of 1970 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 50)
  - Class of 1932 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1973; 1975-1976; 1992; 2002 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 51)
  - Class of 1961 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1973; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 52)
  - Class of 1952 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1972; 1976; 1978; 1992 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 53)
  - Class of 1963 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1973; 1993 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 54)
  - Class of 1926 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1974; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 55)
  - Class of 1924 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1974; 1976; 1978 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 56)
  - Chi Sigma Theta, 1971-1974; 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 57)
  - Class of 1954 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971-1994; Undated (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 58)
  - Class of 1962 Newsletters, 1971-2011 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 59)
  - Class of 1929 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1973-1974; 1976; 1979 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 60)
  - Class of 1921 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1973; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 61)
  - Class of 1939 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1974-1975; 1978-1979; 1993 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 62)
  - Class of 1969 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1974-ca. 1975 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 63)
  - Nation's Capital Branch, 1971; 1974-1976; 1978-1979; 1983-1986 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 64)
  - Class of 1955 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1975-1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 65)
  - Class of 1941 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 66)
  - Class of 1946 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 67)
  - Class of 1966 Newsletters and Reunions, 1971; 1976 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 68)
  - Campus Center Map, 1972 May 12 (Box 3 (4-Class Notes and Communication), Folder 69)